masterofproject.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | Master of Project Academy

## Get Certified at Your Pace

### World's #1 Affordable & Flexible Leading Online Certification Training Provider.   
100% Online and Self-Paced Certification Courses.

## Privacy Policy

**Overview**

You are contracting with Master of Project Academy, Inc. a Delaware corporation located in New York, United States of America ("Master of Project Academy", "We", "Us", or "Our"). We take your privacy seriously and are committed to protecting your right to privacy as a user of our website. We have made every effort to ensure your information is secure. This privacy policy information covers what information is collected, what we do with it, and what you can do about it. You can use this information to make your decisions about your privacy 

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which the website collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a 'User') of the website ('Site'). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Master of Project Academy. 

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities. 

**Payment**

Master of Project Academy does not currently retain credit card numbers internally. We partner with payment providers such as PayPal, Stripe, Teachable and others. All direct payment gateways like Paypal, adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information. 

In "Lifetime" pricing options, your PayPal or credit card will be charged only once. If you subscribed on a "Monthly" pricing option, your credit will be charged monthly automatically by our payment providers such as Stripe or Teachable until you cancel your subscription. 

**Subscription Cancellation**

You can cancel your subscription to any course at any time you wish from your profile under "Subscriptions" menu. After you cancelled your subscription, you will still have access to the course until next charging date and you will be automatically unenrolled from the course on next charging date. 

**30 Day Money Back Guarantee & Refund**

Master of Project Academy provides 30 day money back guarantee and full refund in order to ensure 100% customer satisfaction.30 Day Money Back Guarantee policy of Master of Project Academy should be used in good faith by the members. If Master of Project Academy detects that any member exceeds 10% of total progress and fraudulent activities that shows the customer logged in several times and followed majority of the course, Master of Project Academy preserves the right to refuse refund. 

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. 

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use 'cookies' to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. 

**How we use collected information**

Master of Project Academy may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:  

  * _To improve customer service_  
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  * _To personalize user experience_  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  * _To send periodic emails_  
We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include Master of Project Academy news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. 

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. 

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies. 

**Changes to this privacy policy**

Master of Project Academy has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. 

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
